



        ---------------------------------------------------------------

          Channel ID:      corp
          Channel Name:    Корп
          Listener:        Worm Holera
          Session started: 2023.11.30 15:47:58
        ---------------------------------------------------------------

﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:48:00 ] Система EVE > Канал изменен на Корп: State War Academy*
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:50:18 ] Fresh Queen > .1.000.000 FREE Skill Points to all new players using this link.Click "LOG IN TO BECOME A RECRUIT" and you get 1 million free skill points!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=893701a3-c77d-404e-83e7-913b6c112b86
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:58:37 ] Dr Murphy Cooper > whats the difference in ore, scordite, condensed, massive?
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:59:11 ] Hakkon Anninen > how much minerals you get out of them
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:59:27 ] Hakkon Anninen > condensed is +5% and the other one +10%
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:59:34 ] Dr Murphy Cooper > thanks
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:59:35 ] Destrto3 > Each one gives you a certain percentage more ore
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:59:41 ] Hakkon Anninen > all ores have three types. normal, +5% and +10%
﻿[ 2023.11.30 15:59:56 ] Destrto3 > ^^ Exactly
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:12:27 ] Terilato Otsolen > Click this Link for 1 Million Free Skill Points - works for new and older accounts too (click on "ALREADY HAVE AN ACCOUNT? Log in to Become a Recruit")  Be carefull!Visit only the official game sites!p.s. If you no longer need it, add me to your blacklist so you don't see my message anymore.
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:14:34 ] Munny Hunny > .Happy November!Never referred? Want a free million SP? Tried to refer yourself and found out you can't? Click here! Works for people no matter when they created an account! Just click "Already have an account". If you're a vet, you can buy two extractors, turn them into injectors, and make 750 mil quick! If you're using it for training, it's almost three weeks of training for free; five weeks if you're an Alpha Clone!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=b3f43e97-c079-4689-b621-fc59972e97a5(You can open a tab and get back to it, it's not going away in the next patch.)If you already did, and hate the spam of people who post things like this more than once per channel per hour, right-click their name and click "Block", and you never have to hear it again. :^)
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:23:10 ] Miljala Jisto > Collect your Free 1M Skill Points (20 skilling days equivalent) - Click the link and select 'Log in to become a Recruit'https://www.eveonline.com/fr/signup?invc=309654a4-0485-4c15-b029-ec4e10728a3cFly free
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:24:57 ] Nini Pirkibo > 1,000,000 skill points from official Eve - online site!! - Check it out!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=6218b568-936d-46c2-b4d1-f84cb5f87847
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:25:47 ] Naaiya Kado > and another for my blocklist!
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:31:50 ] Fresh Queen > .1.000.000 FREE Skill Points to all new players using this link.Click "LOG IN TO BECOME A RECRUIT" and you get 1 million free skill points!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=893701a3-c77d-404e-83e7-913b6c112b86
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:37:22 ] Tiga Ekari Aivoras > -=-=Hello-=-=Are you a NEW or RETURNING player??You may be able to collect 1 million skillpoints as part of Eve Online's official Recruitment program. Click the link below and once on Eve website scroll down to "already have an account - sign in to become a recruit". Once you sign in your skillpoints will be delivered to your account via the reward redeem icon in the lower left corner. Thanks, and ENJOY!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=545b5172-d974-435d-825a-b30fd6b96116
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:41:54 ] Tiga Ekari Aivoras > Cybele that ship looks like a giant...
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:46:19 ] Tiga Ekari Aivoras > -=-=Hello-=-=Are you a NEW or RETURNING player??You may be able to collect 1 million skillpoints as part of Eve Online's official Recruitment program. Click the link below and once on Eve website scroll down to "already have an account - sign in to become a recruit". Once you sign in your skillpoints will be delivered to your account via the reward redeem icon in the lower left corner. Thanks, and ENJOY!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=545b5172-d974-435d-825a-b30fd6b96116
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:58:32 ] Fresh Queen > .1.000.000 FREE Skill Points to all new players using this link.Click "LOG IN TO BECOME A RECRUIT" and you get 1 million free skill points!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=893701a3-c77d-404e-83e7-913b6c112b86
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:58:48 ] SpacePsyTrance ownedhard > хрю
﻿[ 2023.11.30 16:59:42 ] Tiga Ekari Aivoras > -=-=Hello-=-=Are you a NEW or RETURNING player??You may be able to collect 1 million skillpoints as part of Eve Online's official Recruitment program. Click the link below and once on Eve website scroll down to "already have an account - sign in to become a recruit". Once you sign in your skillpoints will be delivered to your account via the reward redeem icon in the lower left corner. Thanks, and ENJOY!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=545b5172-d974-435d-825a-b30fd6b96116
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:16:28 ] Don't Tackle 1 > 1,000,000 FREE Skill Points to all new players from Eve's site. Go to:https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=0351c27a-1b92-42c7-81ab-1bffcb6981b8Click "LOG IN TO BECOME A RECRUIT" and you get 1 million free skill points!It also works on old accounts if you have never redeemed the offer before.
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:22:29 ] Munny Hunny > .Happy November!Never referred? Want a free million SP? Tried to refer yourself and found out you can't? Click here! Works for people no matter when they created an account! Just click "Already have an account". If you're a vet, you can buy two extractors, turn them into injectors, and make 750 mil quick! If you're using it for training, it's almost three weeks of training for free; five weeks if you're an Alpha Clone!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=b3f43e97-c079-4689-b621-fc59972e97a5(You can open a tab and get back to it, it's not going away in the next patch.)If you already did, and hate the spam of people who post things like this more than once per channel per hour, right-click their name and click "Block", and you never have to hear it again. :^)
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:25:35 ] Fresh Queen > .1.000.000 FREE Skill Points to all new players using this link.Click "LOG IN TO BECOME A RECRUIT" and you get 1 million free skill points!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=893701a3-c77d-404e-83e7-913b6c112b86
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:34:52 ] Ippa Funaila > Fellow Capsuleers, if you haven't already, use the EVE-link below to secure YOUR free 1 000 000 skillpoints via the official CCP-SP bonus. Once there, select "I already have an account". Then redeem the points in the in-game redeem interface (Bottom left of the UI) and you will be credited with 1 000 000 skillpoints, usable for alpha and omega Accounts, new or old ones. Easily saves you 20-30 days of skill time.https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=2bc49f4b-a327-41a0-859c-81357d508d01
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:40:15 ] Sara Bunny > Melvin Ralph Drauc  Claim your FREE 1 Million Skill Point NOW! Scroll down to log in to be come a recruit! ( 1m SP Immedietly available in claim after)https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=cbfcf0bb-1e2c-401c-b622-a6718201c55f
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:42:09 ] Tiga Ekari Aivoras > -=-=Hello-=-=Are you a NEW or RETURNING player??You may be able to collect 1 million skillpoints as part of Eve Online's official Recruitment program. Click the link below and once on Eve website scroll down to "already have an account - sign in to become a recruit". Once you sign in your skillpoints will be delivered to your account via the reward redeem icon in the lower left corner. Thanks, and ENJOY!https://www.eveonline.com/signup?invc=545b5172-d974-435d-825a-b30fd6b96116
﻿[ 2023.11.30 17:44:47 ] Система EVE > Канал изменен на Корп: Heirs of Holes
